

m johansen@outlook.dk Mobile: 42604044 Charlotte Muncks Vej 20 København 2400



Michael Johansen

PROFILE

Most of my work experience has to do with customer service and communications, as I enjoy creating positive encounters between customers and firm.

As time moved on, I sought new experiences and found myself get a thrill out of programming. Finding solutions for problems I've never come across always makes me proud and motivates me to learn even more.

CORE SKILLS

- Persevering, committed and a quick learner
- Analytical thinking regards to problem-solving/debugging code.
- Strong social and communicative skills.

WORK EXPERIENCE

<u>2021- Current:</u> **Programming tutor, Københavns Erhvervsakademi.**

Assistant teacher/tutor in a homework-cafe for Computer Science students.

<u>2020-2021</u>: Fitness World, Gym-Staff, København.

Primarily tasks surrounding customer service and support, while also managing a gym's inventory and equipment and producing graphs of opinion polls for my colleague.

2011-2016: Fitness World, Receptionist, København and Gentofte.

UDDANNELSE

<u>2020 – Current</u>: **Computer Science**, **Københavns Erhvervsakademi**. (*End Jan 2023*)

<u>2016-2017</u>: **Physics, Københavns Universitet**, Unfinished.

IT SKILLS

Languages:

Javascript, Java, HTML/CSS, Typescript.

Frameworks and libraries:

Node.js, Express, React Native, Svelte, Spring/Thymeleaf, Socket.io, GraphQL.

Database & ORM:

MySQL primarily, introduced to MongoDB and Firebase. IPA, Hibernate.

LANGUAGES

<u>Danish</u> – Native language. <u>English</u> – Fluent.

SPARE TIME

Usually, every weekday contains some sort of physical activity to keep my body healthy or to meet up with friends to enjoy their company. I used to spend a lot of time playing videogames but haven't really had the time since I started this education. Furthermore, I participate in tabletoproleplaying games with my friends, as it is a fun and challenging way to develop my problem-solving skills. I really enjoy the teamwork and coordination that is required to make a good group in the game.